**Privacy Statement  
**

Last Updated on December 16, 2024

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Thank you for visiting the online and mobile resources published by Etison LLC. Our privacy statement, contained in the pages that follow, serves to give notice about the types of personal information we collect, how we use it, who we share it with and why, and what we do to try to protect it. We delve into those matters in a fair amount of detail in the pages that follow. We encourage you to read them carefully. In the meantime, we provide a quick overview below.

**What do we collect?**

There are two types of information that we obtain from you online and then store and use:

• non-personal information that’s collected automatically from each visitor, such as your device operating system; and

• personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or that is collected automatically.

**Why do we use it?**

We use non-personal information to administer our online and mobile resources, make them better, and to make business decisions about what programs our customers might like.

We use voluntarily provided personal information to respond to your inquiries and provide you with the services you have requested, amongst other uses as further described below. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third party data vendors or marketing companies. As you might expect, we disclose your information when required by law.

**When do we share it?**

We share personal information when needed to fulfill our legal obligations and when our vendors and business partners need it to perform under the contracts we have with them. We do not sell or rent any personal information to third party data brokers or marketing companies.

**Your Privacy Choices and Rights**

You do not have to provide personal information to enjoy most of the features of our online and mobile resources. Moreover, you can opt out of certain activities like newsletters and announcements. You may have certain additional rights depending upon the jurisdiction in which you reside, or in which your personal data was collected from, pursuant to the applicable data protection laws.

**Contacting Us**

Questions about this highlights page or our online privacy statement may be sent to Etison LLC, ATTN: Legal & Compliance Department, 3443 W. Bavaria Street, Eagle, Idaho 83616 or [compliance@clickfunnels.com](mailto:compliance@clickfunnels.com) 

The English language version of this privacy statement is the controlling version regardless of any translation you may attempt.

**NAVIGATING THROUGH THIS STATEMENT**

You can use the links below to navigate to areas of this statement that apply specifically to you, or which may otherwise be of interest:

Etison LLC (“**Etison**,” “**us**,” “**we**,” or “**our**”) thanks you for visiting the **online and mobile resources** we publish. We use the words “you” and “your” to mean you, the reader, and other visitors to our online and mobile resources who are, in all cases, over the age of 13. Our privacy statement (“**this statement**,” “**this privacy statement**,” and “**our statement**”) informs you about from whom and the types of personal information we collect, how we use it, who we share it with and why, and what we do to try to protect it. 

**Online and mobile resources** means the websites and other internet features we own that allow you to interact with our websites, as well as apps we’ve created and distributed to let our customers and followers view our online and mobile resources or otherwise interact with the content we provide. 

**WHO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM** 

We may collect personal information from the following groups of data subjects: visitors to, and users of, our online and mobile resources; our customers; current members of our workforce and those who apply for posted jobs; and third party vendors and business partners. 

**Personal information** generally means information that can be used to identify you or that can be easily linked to you (for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address, social security number and date of birth). The privacy laws in some jurisdictions include unique elements in what they consider to be the personal information of the consumers or data subjects they protect. If those laws apply to us, as in the case of the California Consumer Privacy Act (“**CCPA**”) or other U.S. state-level data privacy laws, or the European General Data Protection Regulation (“**GDPR**”), our use of the phrase “personal information” includes the unique elements required by such laws. 

The categories of information we collect from each of these groups, and the ways in which we use it, differs. As you may have noticed, it’s possible that the same person could fall into more than one group. Most of this statement addresses our processing and sharing of personal information collected from visitors to and users of our online and mobile resources and our customers. 

Nonetheless, we collect and retain the types of **professional or employment related personal information** you would expect an employer to have about its existing and former workforce and new job applicants. We provide legally required notices of collection, and describe our use and sharing of the personal information of our workforce and applicants in greater detail in confidential internal human resource manuals and documents accessible to members of our workforce, or by publication on the proprietary workforce/applicant portals and apps we operate. In some cases, such portals and apps may be operated by third parties who transfer the personal information to us. In those situations, the legal responsibility to provide notice usually rests with the third party, not us.

In addition, like all corporate enterprises, we buy goods and services, lease equipment and office space and attend industry events. In doing so, we interact with many existing and potential **vendors and business partners** from whom we necessarily collect certain personal information in connection with our contractual and business relationships. As with our customers, this information is typically limited to minimum business contact information. We use and share personal information collected from our vendors and business partners to manage, administer and perform under our contracts with them, or share information about our products. We describe our use of vendor and business partner personal information in greater detail in our confidential contracts with those parties or on the internal vendor management portals we operate. 

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

There are two types of information that we obtain from you online and then store and use: (i) non-personal information that’s collected automatically from each visitor, such as your device operating system; and (ii) personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or that is collected automatically. 

**_By using our online and mobile resources or purchasing our products or services, you are signifying to us that you agree with this section of our privacy statement and that we may use and disclose your information as described._**

_Voluntarily Submitted Information_

If you participate in certain activities via our online and mobile resources, you may be asked to provide us with information about yourself. The types of personal information we collect in those situations includes **identifiers** (such as your name, email address, physical address, and phone number), **professional information** (such as the business you are in), and **financial account information** (such as your credit card information). We do not sell, rent, or trade voluntarily submitted personal information with third parties.  

If you don’t want us to collect this type of personal information, please don’t provide it. This means you shouldn’t participate in the activities on our online and mobile resources that request or require it and you may want to communicate with us by phone or regular mail instead. Participation is strictly your choice. Not participating may limit your ability to take full advantage of the online and mobile resources, but it will not affect your ability to access certain information available to the general public on the online and mobile resources. 

Some of the ways you voluntarily give us your personal information and how we use it:

**Emails and Online Forms** – When you send us an email or fill out an online form, such as to contact us, your email address and any other personal information (e.g., home address or phone number) that may be in the content of your message or attached to it, are retained by us and used to respond back directly to you and to process your request. Depending on the personal information provided, communications from us may be in the form of emails, telephone calls, and/or text messages. We may also send you information about any of our products or services we think may be of interest to you.

**Registering for an Account** – When you register for an account or you register your child for a sub-account, you submit personal information to us such as your name and email address (or your child’s name and email address) which we then retain. We use that information to create and manage your account and in some cases establish a password and profile to communicate with you and any sub-accounts you created via email.  

**Registering for Events** – When you register for events, conferences or programs we ourselves may host (rather than outsource to a third party event manager with its own privacy policies), you will be submitting the types of identifiers described above. If the event requires a fee, we may also ask you to submit credit card or other financial information. We use this information to register you for the event and send you communications regarding the event.

**Becoming a Subscriber to Our Service** – We use any information provided from our customers to perform our contractual obligations and provide the products and services purchased to them, to manage their accounts and communicate with them.

**Social Media and Community Features** – Some of our online and mobile resources may offer social media-like community features letting users post messages and comments, and/or upload an image or other files and materials. If you choose to make use of these features, the information you post, including your screen name and any other personal information, will be in the public domain and not covered/protected by this statement.

_Automatically Collected Information_  
When you visit our online and mobile resources, basic information is passively collected through your web browser via use of tracking technologies, such as a “cookie” which is a small text file that is downloaded onto your computer or mobile device when you access the online and mobile resources. It allows us to recognize your computer or mobile device and store some information about your preferences or past actions. Additional information can be found in our [Cookie Policy](https://signup.clickfunnels.com/cookie-policy). You can learn more about cookies and tracking technologies in general [here](https://www.ftc.gov/site-information/privacy-policy/internet-cookies).

We allow third party vendors to use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing activities over time following your use of the site. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("**Google**"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how you use the online and mobile resources and enhance your experience when you visit the online and mobile resources. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can learn more about how to opt out of Google Analytics by going to [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Our use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use Requirements.

The internet activity information collected through cookies and other similar means includes such things as: the domain name and IP address from which you accessed our online and mobile resources; the type of browser and operating system you use; the date and time and length of your visit; the specific page visited, graphics viewed and any documents downloaded; the specific links to other sites you accessed from our online and mobile resources; and the specific links from other sites you used to access our online and mobile resources.

Additionally, if you access our online and mobile resources from a phone or other mobile device, the mobile services provider may transmit to us uniquely identifiable mobile device information which allows us to then collect mobile phone numbers and associate them with the mobile device identification information. Some mobile phone vendors also operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices and we may receive this information as well if location services are enabled on your device. If you do not want us to collect and use **geolocation data**, disable location services through your device settings.

Regardless, we use both automatically collected information and mobile device information to compile generic reports about popular pages on our online and mobile resources, and to see how our customers and followers are accessing our online and mobile resources. We then use that data to administer the online and mobile resources and make them better, make your activities more convenient and efficient and to enhance the functionality of our online and mobile resources, such as by remembering certain of your information in order to save you time. 

_Data Retention  
_We use and retain your personal information in accordance with applicable law and as long as necessary to carry out the purposes described above in accordance with our internal data retention procedures. The criteria used to determine our retention periods include: (i) the length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you; (ii) whether there is an applicable legal obligation; or (iii) whether retention is advisable to enforce our agreements, satisfy applicable statutes of limitations, resolve disputes, or manage litigation or regulatory investigations.  

_User Beware: External Sites, Apps, Links and Social Media  
_We maintain a presence on one or more external social media platforms such as Twitter, Facebook, YouTube and LinkedIn. We may further allow features of our online and mobile resources to connect with, or be viewable from, that external social media presence. Similarly, our online and mobile resources may contain links to other websites or apps controlled by third parties. 

We are not responsible for either the content on, or the privacy practices of, social media platforms, or any third party sites or apps to which we link. Those apps, sites and platforms are not controlled by us and therefore have their own privacy policies and terms of use. If you have questions about how those apps, sites and platforms collect and use personal information, you should carefully read their privacy policies and contact them using the information they provide. 

**WHEN/WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use non-personal information to administer our online and mobile resources, make them better, and to make business decisions about what programs our customers might like.

We use voluntarily provided personal information for our legitimate interests, including to respond to your inquiries and provide you with the services you have requested, amongst other uses as further described below. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third party data vendors or marketing companies. As you might expect, we disclose your information when required by law. We may use your personal information when we have your consent to do so, where required or permitted under applicable law.

_Affiliates._

In addition to those third parties set forth above, we may share your information, including personal information, within our family of companies. Those companies will use such information in generally the same manner as we do under this privacy statement which includes sending you information about their products, services, or initiatives that may be of interest to you.

_Legally Compelled Disclosures._

We may disclose your information, including personal information, to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by such government authorities, or at our discretion or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to responding to court orders and subpoenas. 

_To Prevent Harm._

We may disclose your information, including personal information, when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the online and mobile resources, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

_Business Transfer._

If we or any of our affiliates, or substantially all of its or their assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation, or liquidation, personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

_Vendors and Business Partners._

We may share your information, including personal information, with our vendors and other third parties with whom we have a contractual relationship. We may also share your information, including personal information, with vendors who provide third party software services that you have chosen to assist you with your sales funnels. We do our best to disclose only the information each of those parties need.

We have adopted standards for those vendors and business partners who receive personal information from us. We attempt to bind such vendors and business partners to those standards via written contracts. We further attempt to contractually restrict what our vendors and business partners can do with the personal information we provide to them such that it is used only to the extent necessary to carry out the business purpose for which it was provided; is not disclosed to anyone else without our consent or under our instruction; remains, as between us and the applicable vendor or business partner, our property; and is not transferred out of the United States without our consent. 

_**Please note, however, that we cannot guarantee that all of our vendors and business partners will agree to these contractual requirements; nor can we ensure that, even when they do agree, they will always fully comply.**_

**YOUR RIGHTS AND OPTIONS**

You can choose not to provide personal information, but in doing so some of the features of our online and mobile resources may not be available to you. Moreover, you can opt out of certain activities like newsletters and announcements. Data subjects in certain locations, or whose personal data was obtained while they were in certain locations, may have additional rights pursuant to the applicable data protection laws.

**GDPR Jurisdictions** means the countries composed of the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, Switzerland and Japan which, having received an “adequacy decision” from the European Commission, adheres to the material terms of the GDPR.

If we are using personal information you provided to us in order to enable us to send you materials, such as newsletters or product alerts via text or email, and you decide you don’t want to receive such materials, you may opt out by following the opt-out instructions in the email or other communication (e.g., by responding to the text with “STOP”), or by contacting us using the contact information below. When we receive your request, we will take reasonable steps to remove your name from our distribution lists. You need to understand it may take a period of time to remove your name from our lists after your request and due to such latency you may still receive materials for a period of time after you opt out. In addition to opting out, you have the ability to access, amend, and delete your personal information by contacting us using the contact information below.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY** 

Federal laws impose special restrictions and obligations on commercial website operators who direct their operations toward, and collect and use information from, children under the age of 13. We take those age-related requirements very seriously, and consistent with it do not intend for our online and mobile resources to be used by children under the age of 13 without first obtaining the verifiable consent of such child’s parent or legal guardian. Moreover, we do not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 13, only a parent or legal guardian may provide such information after adhering to our verification process for submitting such information via the online and mobile resources. If we become aware that anyone under the age of 18 has submitted personal information to our online and mobile resources without such parental or legal guardian approval and that is not an integral part to accessing or using our Services, we will delete that information and will not use it for any purpose whatsoever. If you believe that someone under the age of 18 has submitted personal information to our online and mobile resources, please contact us at [compliance@clickfunnels.com](mailto:compliance@clickfunnels.com). We encourage parents and legal guardians to talk with their children about the potential risks of providing personal information over the Internet.

**HOW WE PROTECT COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will take all reasonable security precautions to protect your personal information provided to our online and mobile resources. We have adopted a security program that includes technical, organizational, administrative, and other security measures designed to protect, in a manner consistent with accepted industry standards and applicable law, against anticipated or actual threats to the security of personal information (the “**Security Program**”). We cannot, however, guarantee that your information, whether during transmission or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be free from unauthorized access or that loss, misuse, destruction, or alteration will not occur. Except for our duty to maintain the Security Program under applicable law, we disclaim any other liability for any such theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications including personal information. We have every reason to believe our Security Program is reasonable and appropriate for our business and the nature of foreseeable risks to the personal information we collect. We further periodically review and update our Security Program, including as required by applicable law.

Nonetheless, as part of our Security Program, we have specific incident response and management procedures that are activated whenever we become aware that your personal information was likely to have been compromised. We further require, as part of our vendor and business partner oversight procedures, that such parties notify us immediately if they have any reason to believe that an incident adversely affecting personal information we provided to them has occurred. 

**U.S. STATE PRIVACY LAWS**

This section applies to visitors, users, and others who reside in the state of California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, and Montana, USA (collectively the “Designated States”). When we collect personal information from residents of the Designated States, where applicable we become subject to, and those residents have rights under, the U.S. state level data privacy laws, such as the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), as amended (collectively, "State Data Privacy Laws"). This section of our statement is used to allow us to fulfill our obligations under State Data Privacy Laws and explain your CCPA rights. For purposes of this section, “Personal Information” has the meaning given in these State Data Privacy Laws.

**What did we collect from Residents of the Designated States?**

The chart below summarizes how we collect, use and share various categories of your Personal Information, indicating the sources from which we collect Personal Information, the business purposes for which Personal Information is collected and/or shared, and the categories of third parties with whom Personal Information is shared, describing our practices during the 12 months preceding the effective date of this Privacy Statement. We will not collect additional categories of Personal Information or use the Personal Information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice and obtaining your consent where required by law.

In the past 12 months, we shared or disclosed all of the categories of Personal Information listed below for the business purposes specified.

CUSTOM JAVASCRIPT / HTML

\*\*Categories of third parties with which Personal Information is shared/disclosed:  

We may share your Personal Information with the following categories of third parties for a business purpose:

1\. Affiliate companies

2\. Service providers and subcontractors including internet service providers, cloud service providers, data analytics providers, email marketing providers, and operating systems/platforms

3\. Third parties for marketing and analytics services including advertising networks, data analytics providers, social networks, market research providers

4\. Professional advisors (such as accountants, auditors)

Personal information may be shared with government authorities on a case-by-case basis upon receipt of a lawful request, or where required by law. In the event of a sale or transfer of some or all of Etison’s business or assets, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you if your Personal Information will be shared with parties to the transaction(s).

Although we do not and have not "sold" Personal Information to a third party for money in the past 12 months, we disclose information to third parties in a manner that may be considered a "sale" as defined under State Data Privacy Laws. Specifically, the categories of Personal Information that are disclosed to third parties in this manner include Identifiers, Characteristics of Protected Classifications, Commercial Information, Geolocation Data, and Inferences; and the categories of third parties receiving these disclosures are companies that operate cookies and other online tracking technologies. Along with third parties providing us with marketing and analytics services, we use Personal Information for targeted advertising purposes.

See the section entitled “Data Retention” above for a description of the criteria used to determine how long we retain Personal Information. We do not use or disclose sensitive Personal Information for purposes other than those specified in CCPA Regulations Section 7207 (m).

**Rights of the Designated States**

You may have the following rights under the State Data Privacy Laws, where applicable:

1\. You have the right to a copy of your Personal Information in our possession, or to request information about the categories of Personal Information we have collected about you, the categories of sources from which we collected the Personal Information, the purposes for collecting, sharing or selling the Personal Information (where applicable), the categories of third parties with whom we have shared or sold your Personal Information, the purpose for which we shared or sold your Personal Information, and information about the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.

2\. You have the right to request that we correct in our records any Personal Information about you that is inaccurate.

3\. You have the right to request the deletion of Personal Information that we collected about you and retained, subject to certain exceptions.

4\. You have the right to opt out of the sale or sharing of your Personal Information with third parties for targeted advertising purposes, where such a “sale” or “sharing" is occurring (as such terms are defined by applicable law). 

5\. You have the right to limit the use or disclosure of your sensitive Personal Information, where collected and as permitted under the State Data Privacy Laws.

To exercise these rights, you may submit your privacy choices [here](#https://compliance.myclickfunnels.com/data-rights-request?_gl=1*1vkoo9q*_ga*NTc3MjU4ODE1LjE2ODQ1MTk2MTk.*_ga_XJMXXSCP9Q*MTY4NDUxOTYxOS4xLjEuMTY4NDUyMzAwNy41OS4wLjA.). You may also contact us at [compliance@clickfunnels.com](#compliance@clickfunnels.com) or **1-888-411-0243**. You can exercise these rights up to two different times every 12 months. The State Data Privacy Laws only allows us to act on your request if we can verify your identity or your authority to make the request so you will also need to follow our instructions for identity verification. We will verify your identity by asking you to provide identifying information that we will match to information in our records. Only you or a person that you authorize in writing to act on your behalf may make a verifiable consumer request related to your Personal Information. You (or your authorized agent) must provide documentation signed by you demonstrating that the agent is authorized to submit a verifiable consumer request on your behalf.

If you make a verifiable request per the above, we will confirm our receipt and respond in the time frames specified in State Data Privacy Laws. If you would like to appeal our decision related to a request to exercise your rights under this Privacy Statement, please contact us at the email address or phone number listed above. All appeal requests must be made within a reasonable amount of time after receipt of our response to your verifiable consumer request. 

It’s important to us that you know that if you exercise these rights, we will not “discriminate” against you by treating you differently from other individuals who use our sites and mobile resources or purchase our services but do not exercise their rights. We do not charge a different price or rate or provide a different level or quality of goods or services based on you exercising your privacy rights.

**THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION** 

We do collect or otherwise obtain personal information from data subjects located in the GDPR Jurisdictions. We fulfill our GDPR obligations with respect to our workforce/job applicants, our customers (and their own end-clients), and our vendors and business partners through a series of separate notices, contracts or other terms provided to them at the time, and in the manner and form, GDPR and local law within each GDPR Jurisdiction requires. 

We describe, in the immediately following section of this statement, how we comply with the GDPR for personal information collected from visitors to and users of our online and mobile resources while they were in a GDPR Jurisdiction. Thus for purposes of that section, the words “you” and “your” mean only such GDPR Jurisdiction-based visitors and users. 

**What do we collect from you in the GDPR Jurisdictions and how do we use it?**

We collect from you the categories of personal information already described. The lawful basis on which we rely for such collection, later use and disclosure, is what the GDPR refers to as legitimate interest. As stated elsewhere in this statement, we do not sell any of your personal information to third parties nor do we use it for automated decision making.

**Cross-border Data Transfers and Third Party Processors** 

If we transfer personal information from the GDPR Jurisdictions to a location that has not been deemed by the European Commission to have adequate privacy protections, we do so in the manner the GDPR permits. 

**Rights of Data Subjects in the GDPR Jurisdictions** 

While we attempt to allow all visitors and users of our online and mobile resources to exercise a degree of control over their personal information, under the GDPR we have a legal obligation to do so for you. More specifically, with respect to personal information collected from you while you were in a GDPR Jurisdiction, you have these rights: transparency, access, correction and deletion, portability, who, what, why and where, and restriction/objection (for more information click [here](https://gdpr-info.eu/chapter-3/)).

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact compliance@clickfunnels.com. Your ability to exercise these rights is subject to certain conditions and exemptions that you can read about in Articles 12 through 23 of the GDPR. Among those conditions is our right to decline part or all of a request if we cannot satisfy our reasonable doubts and concerns about your identity in a manner that helps us minimize the risk that unauthorized persons might use a GDPR right to access your personal information. We will respond to all requests without undue delay, and in accordance with the time frames, if any, prescribed by the GDPR. If you are not satisfied with how we use your personal information or respond to your requests, you have the right to complain to your data protection regulator. Contact information for the EU data protection regulators can be found [here](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).  

Pursuant to Article 27 of the GDPR, you may contact our EU representative using the following contact information:

You can exercise these rights, you may submit your privacy choices [here](#https://compliance.myclickfunnels.com/data-rights-request?_gl=1*1vkoo9q*_ga*NTc3MjU4ODE1LjE2ODQ1MTk2MTk.*_ga_XJMXXSCP9Q*MTY4NDUxOTYxOS4xLjEuMTY4NDUyMzAwNy41OS4wLjA.). You may also contact us at compliance@clickfunnels.com or **1-888-411-0243**. You can exercise these rights up to two different times every 12 months. The CCPA only allows us to act on your request if we can verify your identity or your authority to make the request so you will also need to follow our instructions for identity verification. We will verify your identity by asking you to provide identifying information that we will match to information in our records. Only you or a person that you authorize in writing to act on your behalf may make a verifiable consumer request related to your Personal Information. You (or your authorized agent) must provide documentation signed by you demonstrating that the agent is authorized to submit a verifiable consumer request on your behalf.

If you make a verifiable request per the above, we will confirm our receipt and respond in the time frames prescribed by the CCPA. 

It’s important to us that you know that if you exercise these rights, we will not “discriminate” against you by treating you differently from other California residents who use our sites and mobile resources or purchase our services but do not exercise their rights. We do not charge a different price or rate or provide a different level or quality of goods or services based on you exercising your privacy rights.

**THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION** 

We do collect or otherwise obtain personal information from data subjects located in the GDPR Jurisdictions. We fulfill our GDPR obligations with respect to our workforce/job applicants, our customers (and their own end-clients), and our vendors and business partners through a series of separate notices, contracts or other terms provided to them at the time, and in the manner and form, GDPR and local law within each GDPR Jurisdiction requires. 

We describe, in the immediately following section of this statement, how we comply with the GDPR for personal information collected from visitors to and users of our online and mobile resources while they were in a GDPR Jurisdiction. Thus for purposes of that section, the words “you” and “your” mean only such GDPR Jurisdiction-based visitors and users. 

**What do we collect from you in the GDPR Jurisdictions and how do we use it?**

We collect from you the categories of personal information already described. The lawful basis on which we rely for such collection, later use and disclosure, is what the GDPR refers to as legitimate interest. As stated elsewhere in this statement, we do not sell any of your personal information to third parties nor do we use it for automated decision making.

**Cross-border Data Transfers and Third Party Processors** 

If we transfer personal information from the GDPR Jurisdictions to a location that has not been deemed by the European Commission to have adequate privacy protections, we do so in the manner the GDPR permits. 

**Rights of Data Subjects in the GDPR Jurisdictions** 

While we attempt to allow all visitors and users of our online and mobile resources to exercise a degree of control over their personal information, under the GDPR we have a legal obligation to do so for you. More specifically, with respect to personal information collected from you while you were in a GDPR Jurisdiction, you have these rights: transparency, access, correction and deletion, portability, who, what, why and where, and restriction/objection (for more information click [here](https://gdpr-info.eu/chapter-3/)).

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact compliance@clickfunnels.com. Your ability to exercise these rights is subject to certain conditions and exemptions that you can read about in Articles 12 through 23 of the GDPR. Among those conditions is our right to decline part or all of a request if we cannot satisfy our reasonable doubts and concerns about your identity in a manner that helps us minimize the risk that unauthorized persons might use a GDPR right to access your personal information. We will respond to all requests without undue delay, and in accordance with the time frames, if any, prescribed by the GDPR. If you are not satisfied with how we use your personal information or respond to your requests, you have the right to complain to your data protection regulator. Contact information for the EU data protection regulators can be found [here](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).  

Pursuant to Article 27 of the GDPR, you may contact our EU representative using the following contact information:

IITR Datenschutz GmbH

Marienplatz 2, 80331 München, Germany

email@iitr.de

089-18917360

**RIGHTS OF DATA SUBJECTS IN OTHER JURISDICTIONS**

In other jurisdictions, with similar data privacy regulations, we may collect from you the categories of personal information already described. We collect and manage (including disclose) such data in compliance with applicable local law(s). As noted, we do not sell any of your personal information to third parties nor do we use it for automated decision making.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

The English language version of this privacy statement is the controlling version regardless of any translation you may attempt. 

We reserve the right to change or update this statement from time to time. Please check our online and mobile resources periodically for such changes since all information collected is subject to the statement in place at that time.

**CONTACTING US**

         If you have questions about our privacy statement or privacy practices, please contact us at:

Etison LLC

Attn: Legal & Compliance Department

3443 W. Bavaria Street

Eagle, Idaho 83616

English
=======

PRIVACY STATEMENT

PRIVACY, SECURITY AND TRANSPARENCY

Thank you for visiting the online and mobile resources published by Etison, LLC. Our privacy statement, contained in the pages that follow, serves, to give notice about the types of personal information we collect, how we use it, who we share it with and why, and what we do to try to protect it. We delve into those matters in a fair amount of detail in the pages that follow. We encourage you to read them carefully. In the meantime, we provide a quick overview below.

What do we collect?

There are two types of information that we obtain from you online and then store and use:

* non-personal information that’s collected automatically from each visitor, such as your device operating system; and

* personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or that is collected automatically.

Why do we use it?

We use non-personal information to administer our online and mobile resources, make them better, and to make business decisions about what programs our customers might like.

We use voluntarily provided personal information to respond to your inquiries and provide you with the services you have requested, amongst other uses as further described below. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third party data vendors or marketing companies. As you might expect, we disclose your information when required by law.

When do we share it?

We share personal information when needed to fulfill our legal obligations and when our vendors and business partners need it to perform under the contracts we have with them. We do not sell or rent any personal information to third party data brokers or marketing companies.

Your Privacy Choices and Rights

You do not have to provide personal information to enjoy most of the features of our online and mobile resources. Moreover, you can opt out of certain activities like newsletters and announcements.  You may have certain additional rights depending upon the jurisdiction in which you reside, or in which your personal data was collected from, pursuant to the applicable data protection laws.

Contacting Us

Questions about this highlights page or our online privacy statement may be sent to Etison, LLC, ATTN: Legal & Compliance Department, 3443 W. Bavaria Street, Eagle, Idaho 83616 or compliance@clickfunnels.com

The English language version of this privacy statement is the controlling version regardless of any translation you may attempt.

NAVIGATING THROUGH THIS STATEMENT

You can use the links below to navigate to areas of this statement that apply specifically to you, or which may otherwise be of interest:

Etison, LLC (“Etison,” “us,” “we,” or “our”) thanks you for visiting the online and mobile resources we publish. We use the words “you” and “your” to mean you, the reader, and other visitors to our online and mobile resources who are, in all cases, over the age of 13.  Our privacy statement (“this statement,” “this privacy statement,” and “our statement”) informs you about from whom and the types of personal information we collect, how we use it, who we share it with and why, and what we do to try to protect it.

Online and mobile resources means the websites and other internet features we own that allow you to interact with our websites, as well as apps we’ve created and distributed to let our customers and followers view our online and mobile resources or otherwise interact with the content we provide.

WHO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM

We may collect personal information from the following groups of data subjects: visitors to, and users of, our online and mobile resources; our customers; current members of our workforce and those who apply for posted jobs; and third party vendors and business partners.

Personal information generally means information that can be used to identify you or that can be easily linked to you (for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address, social security number and date of birth). The privacy laws in some jurisdictions include unique elements in what they consider to be the personal information of the consumers or data subjects they protect. If those laws apply to us, as in the case of the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) or European General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), our use of the phrase “personal information” includes the unique elements required by such laws.

The categories of information we collect from each of these groups, and the ways in which we use it, differs. As you may have noticed, it’s possible that the same person could fall into more than one group. Most of this statement addresses our processing and sharing of personal information collected from visitors to and users of our online and mobile resources and our customers.

Nonetheless, we collect and retain the types of professional or employment related personal information you would expect an employer to have about its existing and former workforce and new job applicants. We provide legally required notices of collection, and describe our use and sharing of the personal information of our workforce and applicants in greater detail in confidential internal human resource manuals and documents accessible to members of our workforce, or by publication on the proprietary workforce/applicant portals and apps we operate. In some cases, such portals and apps may be operated by third parties who transfer the personal information to us. In those situations, the legal responsibility to provide notice usually rests with the third party, not us.

In addition, like all corporate enterprises, we buy goods and services, lease equipment and office space and attend industry events. In doing so, we interact with many existing and potential vendors and business partners from whom we necessarily collect certain personal information in connection with our contractual and business relationships. As with our customers, this information is typically limited to minimum business contact information. We use and share personal information collected from our vendors and business partners to manage, administer and perform under our contracts with them, or share information about our products. We describe our use of vendor and business partner personal information in greater detail in our confidential contracts with those parties or on the internal vendor management portals we operate.

WHAT WE COLLECT

There are two types of information that we obtain from you online and then store and use: (i) non-personal information that’s collected automatically from each visitor, such as your device operating system; and (ii) personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or that is collected automatically.

By using our online and mobile resources or purchasing our products or services, you are signifying to us that you agree with this section of our privacy statement and that we may use and disclose your information as described.

Voluntarily Submitted Information. 

If you participate in certain activities via our online and mobile resources, you may be asked to provide us with information about yourself. The types of personal information we collect in those situations includes identifiers (such as your name, email address, physical address, and phone number), professional information (such as the business you are in), and financial account information (such as your credit card information). We do not sell, rent, or trade voluntarily submitted personal information with third parties.  

If you don’t want us to collect this type of personal information, please don’t provide it. This means you shouldn’t participate in the activities on our online and mobile resources that request or require it and you may want to communicate with us by phone or regular mail instead. Participation is strictly your choice. Not participating may limit your ability to take full advantage of the online and mobile resources, but it will not affect your ability to access certain information available to the general public on the online and mobile resources.

Some of the ways you voluntarily give us your personal information and how we use it:

Emails and Online Forms – When you send us an email or fill out an online form, such as to contact us, your email address and any other personal information (e.g., home address or phone number) that may be in the content of your message or attached to it, are retained by us and used to respond back directly to you and to process your request. Depending on the personal information provided, communications from us may be in the form of emails, telephone calls, and/or text messages. We may also send you information about any of our products or services we think may be of interest to you.

Registering for an Account – When you register for an account or you register your child for a sub-account, you submit personal information to us such as your name and email address (or your child’s name and email address) which we then retain. We use that information to create and manage your account and in some cases establish a password and profile to communicate with you and any sub-accounts you created via email.  

Registering for Events – When you register for events, conferences or programs we ourselves may host (rather than outsource to a third party event manager with its own privacy policies), you will be submitting the types of identifiers described above. If the event requires a fee, we may also ask you to submit credit card or other financial information. We use this information to register you for the event and send you communications regarding the event.

Becoming a Subscriber to Our Service – We use any information provided from our customers to perform our contractual obligations and provide the products and services purchased to them, to manage their accounts and communicate with them.

Social Media and Community Features – Some of our online and mobile resources may offer social media-like community features letting users post messages and comments, and/or upload an image or other files and materials. If you choose to make use of these features, the information you post, including your screen name and any other personal information, will be in the public domain and not covered/protected by this statement.

Automatically Collected Information.

When you visit our online and mobile resources, basic information is passively collected through your web browser via use of tracking technologies, such as a “cookie” which is a small text file that is downloaded onto your computer or mobile device when you access the online and mobile resources. It allows us to recognize your computer or mobile device and store some information about your preferences or past actions. Additional information can be found in our [Cookie Policy](https://signup.clickfunnels.com/cookie-policy). You can learn more about cookies and tracking technologies in general [here](https://www.ftc.gov/site-information/privacy-policy/internet-cookies).

We allow third party vendors to use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing activities over time following your use of the site. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how you use the online and mobile resources and enhance your experience when you visit the online and mobile resources. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can learn more about how to opt out of Google Analytics by going to [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

The internet activity information collected through cookies and other similar means includes such things as: the domain name and IP address from which you accessed our online and mobile resources; the type of browser and operating system you use; the date and time and length of your visit; the specific page visited, graphics viewed and any documents downloaded; the specific links to other sites you accessed from our online and mobile resources; and the specific links from other sites you used to access our online and mobile resources.

Additionally, if you access our online and mobile resources from a phone or other mobile device, the mobile services provider may transmit to us uniquely identifiable mobile device information which allows us to then collect mobile phone numbers and associate them with the mobile device identification information. Some mobile phone vendors also operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices and we may receive this information as well if location services are enabled on your device. If you do not want us to collect and use geolocation data, disable location services through your device settings.

Regardless, we use both automatically collected information and mobile device information to compile generic reports about popular pages on our online and mobile resources, and to see how our customers and followers are accessing our online and mobile resources. We then use that data to administer the online and mobile resources and make them better, make your activities more convenient and efficient and to enhance the functionality of our online and mobile resources, such as by remembering certain of your information in order to save you time.

We use and retain your personal information in accordance with applicable law and as long as necessary to carry out the purposes described above in accordance with our internal data retention procedures.

User Beware: External Sites, Apps, Links and Social Media.

We maintain a presence on one or more external social media platforms such as Twitter, Facebook, YouTube and LinkedIn. We may further allow features of our online and mobile resources to connect with, or be viewable from, that external social media presence. Similarly, our online and mobile resources may contain links to other websites or apps controlled by third parties.

We are not responsible for either the content on, or the privacy practices of, social media platforms, or any third party sites or apps to which we link. Those apps, sites and platforms are not controlled by us and therefore have their own privacy policies and terms of use. If you have questions about how those apps, sites and platforms collect and use personal information, you should carefully read their privacy policies and contact them using the information they provide.

WHEN/WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use non-personal information to administer our online and mobile resources, make them better, and to make business decisions about what programs our customers might like.

We use voluntarily provided personal information for our legitimate interests, including to respond to your inquiries and provide you with the services you have requested, amongst other uses as further described below. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third party data vendors or marketing companies. As you might expect, we disclose your information when required by law. We may use your personal information when we have your consent to do so, where required or permitted under applicable law.

Affiliates.

In addition to those third parties set forth above, we may share your information, including personal information, within our family of companies. Those companies will use such information in generally the same manner as we do under this privacy statement which includes sending you information about their products, services, or initiatives that may be of interest to you.  

Legally Compelled Disclosures.

We may disclose your information, including personal information, to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by such government authorities, or at our discretion or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to responding to court orders and subpoenas.

To Prevent Harm.

We may disclose your information, including personal information, when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the online and mobile resources, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

Business Transfer.

If we or any of our affiliates, or substantially all of its or their assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation, or liquidation, personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Vendors and Business Partners.

We may share your information, including personal information, with our vendors and other third parties with whom we have a contractual relationship. We may also share your information, including personal information, with vendors who provide third party software services that you have chosen to assist you with your sales funnels. We do our best to disclose only the information each of those parties need.

We have adopted standards for those vendors and business partners who receive personal information from us. We attempt to bind such vendors and business partners to those standards via written contracts. We further attempt to contractually restrict what our vendors and business partners can do with the personal information we provide to them such that it is used only to the extent necessary to carry out the business purpose for which it was provided; is not disclosed to anyone else without our consent or under our instruction; remains, as between us and the applicable vendor or business partner, our property; and is not transferred out of the United States without our consent.

Please note, however, that we cannot guarantee that all of our vendors and business partners will agree to these contractual requirements; nor can we ensure that, even when they do agree, they will always fully comply.

YOUR RIGHTS AND OPTIONS

You can choose not to provide personal information, but in doing so some of the features of our online and mobile resources may not be available to you. Moreover, you can opt out of certain activities like newsletters and announcements. Data subjects in certain locations, or whose personal data was obtained while they were in certain locations, may have additional rights pursuant to the applicable data protection laws

GDPR Jurisdictions means the countries composed of the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom (which soon will leave the European Union), Switzerland and Japan which, having received an “adequacy decision” from the European Commission, adheres to the material terms of the GDPR.

If we are using personal information you provided to us in order to enable us to send you materials, such as newsletters or product alerts via text or email, and you decide you don’t want to receive such materials, you may opt out by following the opt-out instructions in the email or other communication (e.g., by responding to the text with “STOP”), or by contacting us using the contact information below. When we receive your request, we will take reasonable steps to remove your name from our distribution lists. You need to understand it may take a period of time to remove your name from our lists after your request and due to such latency you may still receive materials for a period of time after you opt out. In addition to opting out, you have the ability to access, amend, and delete your personal information by contacting us using the contact information below.

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not specifically respond to browser “do not track” signals.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY 

Federal laws impose special restrictions and obligations on commercial website operators who direct their operations toward, and collect and use information from, children under the age of 13. We take those age-related requirements very seriously, and consistent with it do not intend for our online and mobile resources to be used by children under the age of 13 without first obtaining the verifiable consent of such child’s parent or legal guardian. Moreover, we do not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 13, only a parent or legal guardian may provide such information after adhering to our verification process for submitting such information via the online and mobile resources. If we become aware that anyone under the age of 18 has submitted personal information  to our online and mobile resources without such parental or legal guardian approval and that is not an integral part to accessing or using our Services, we will delete that information and will not use it for any purpose whatsoever. If you believe that someone under the age of 18 has submitted personal information to our online and mobile resources, please contact us at compliance@clickfunnels.com. We encourage parents and legal guardians to talk with their children about the potential risks of providing personal information over the Internet.

HOW WE PROTECT COLLECTED PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will take all reasonable security precautions to protect your personal information provided to our online and mobile resources. We have adopted a security program that includes technical, organizational, administrative, and other security measures designed to protect, in a manner consistent with accepted industry standards and applicable law, against anticipated or actual threats to the security of personal information (the “Security Program”). We cannot, however, guarantee that your information, whether during transmission or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be free from unauthorized access or that loss, misuse, destruction, or alteration will not occur. Except for our duty to maintain the Security Program under applicable law, we disclaim any other liability for any such theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications including personal information. We have every reason to believe our Security Program is reasonable and appropriate for our business and the nature of foreseeable risks to the personal information we collect. We further periodically review and update our Security Program, including as required by applicable law.

Nonetheless, as part of our Security Program, we have specific incident response and management procedures that are activated whenever we become aware that your personal information was likely to have been compromised. We further require, as part of our vendor and business partner oversight procedures, that such parties notify us immediately if they have any reason to believe that an incident adversely affecting personal information we provided to them has occurred.

THE CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT

When we collect personal information from California residents we become subject to, and those residents have rights under, the California Consumer Privacy Act or “CCPA”. This section of our statement is used to allow us to fulfill our CCPA obligations and explain your CCPA rights. For purposes of this section, the words “you” and “your” mean only such California residents.

What did we collect from California Residents?

We collect the following categories of personal information: identifiers such as name, address, IP address, and other similar identifiers; personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80 (California customer records statute) such as a name, address, telephone number, credit card number; commercial information such as products or services purchased; internet/electronic activity such as browsing history and search history; geolocation data including geographic coordinates/physical location; and audio, video, electronic or other similar information.  We have disclosed these categories of personal information for a business purpose within the last 12 months. We do not sell, and within the last 12 months have not sold, personal information to third parties.

Rights of California Residents

You have the following rights under the CCPA, in summary disclosure, access and delete. More information can be found [here](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division=3.&part=4.&lawCode=CIV&title=1.81.5). It’s important to us that you know that if you exercise these rights, we will not “discriminate” against you by treating you differently from other California residents who use our sites and mobile resources or purchase our services but do not exercise their rights.

You can exercise these rights up to two different times every 12 months. To do so, just contact us at compliance@clickfunnels.com or 1-888-411-0243. We may ask you to fill out a request form. The CCPA only allows us to act on your request if we can verify your identity or your authority to make the request so you will also need to follow our instructions for identity verification.

If you make a verifiable request per the above, we will confirm our receipt and respond in the time frames prescribed by the CCPA.

THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION

We do collect or otherwise obtain personal information from data subjects located in the GDPR Jurisdictions.  We fulfill our GDPR obligations with respect to our workforce/job applicants, our customers (and their own end-clients), and our vendors and business partners through a series of separate notices, contracts or other terms provided to them at the time, and in the manner and form, GDPR and local law within each GDPR Jurisdiction requires.

We describe, in the immediately following section of this statement, how we comply with the GDPR for personal information collected from visitors to and users of our online and mobile resources while they were in a GDPR Jurisdiction. Thus for purposes of that section, the words “you” and “your” mean only such GDPR Jurisdiction-based visitors and users.

What do we collect from you in the GDPR Jurisdictions and how do we use it?

We collect from you the categories of personal information already described. The lawful basis on which we rely for such collection, later use and disclosure, is what the GDPR refers to as legitimate interest. As stated elsewhere in this statement, [we do not sell](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IsC3CDKHhPuVz2BTBhZqviqVPkajZaHNTu3RSR_A_gA/edit%23bookmark%3Did.2s8eyo1) any of your personal information to third parties nor do we use it for automated decision making.

Cross-border Data Transfers and Third Party Processors

If we transfer personal information from the GDPR Jurisdictions to a location that has not been deemed by the European Commission to have adequate privacy protections, we do so in the manner the GDPR permits.

Rights of Data Subjects in the GDPR Jurisdictions

While we attempt to allow all visitors and users of our online and mobile resources to exercise a degree of control over their personal information, under the GDPR we have a legal obligation to do so for you. More specifically, with respect to personal information collected from you while you were in a GDPR Jurisdiction, you have these rights: transparency, access, correction and deletion, portability, who, what, why and where, and restriction/objection (for more information click [here](https://gdpr-info.eu/chapter-3/)).

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact compliance@clickfunnels.com. Your ability to exercise these rights is subject to certain conditions and exemptions that you can read about in Articles 12 through 23 of the GDPR.  Among those conditions is our right to decline part or all of a request if we cannot satisfy our reasonable doubts and concerns about your identity in a manner that helps us minimize the risk that unauthorized persons might use a GDPR right to access your personal information. We will respond to all requests without undue delay, and in accordance with the time frames, if any, prescribed by the GDPR. If you are not satisfied with how we use your personal information or respond to your requests, you have the right to complain to your data protection regulator. Contact information for the EU data protection regulators can be found [here](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).  

Pursuant to Article 27 of the GDPR, you may contact our EU representative using the following contact information:

IITR Datenschutz GmbH

Marienplatz 2, 80331 München, Germany

email@iitr.de

089-1891736

RIGHTS OF DATA SUBJECTS IN OTHER JURISDICTIONS

In other jurisdictions, with similar data privacy regulations, we may collect from you the categories of personal information already described. We collect and manage (including disclose) such data in compliance with applicable local law(s). As noted, we do not sell any of your personal information to third parties nor do we use it for automated decision making.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

The English language version of this privacy statement is the controlling version regardless of any translation you may attempt.

We reserve the right to change or update this statement from time to time. Please check our online and mobile resources periodically for such changes since all information collected is subject to the statement in place at that time.

CONTACTING US

If you have questions about our privacy statement or privacy practices, please contact us at:

Etison, LLC

Attn: Legal & Compliance Department

3443 W. Bavaria Street

Eagle, Idaho 83616

compliance@clickfunnels.com

Spanish
=======

DECLARACIÓN DE PRIVACIDAD

PRIVACIDAD, SEGURIDAD Y TRANSPARENCIA

Gracias por visitar los recursos virtuales publicados por Etison, LLC. Nuestra declaración de privacidad, contenida en las siguientes páginas, sirve para informar acerca del tipo de información personal que reunimos, cómo la utilizamos, con quién la compartimos y por qué, y qué hacemos para tratar de protegerla. Profundizamos en estas cuestiones con gran cantidad de detalles en las siguientes páginas. Los alentamos a leerlas detalladamente. Mientras tanto, brindaremos una rápida visión general aquí abajo.

¿Qué recopilamos?

Hay dos tipos de información que obtenemos a partir de su actividad en línea, y que luego almacenamos y utilizamos:

* información no personal que se recopila automáticamente de cada visitante, como tu el sistema operativo de su dispositivo; y

* la información personal que usted nos brinda de forma voluntaria o que se recopila automáticamente.

¿Por qué la utilizamos?

Utilizamos información no personal para administrar nuestros recursos virtuales, mejorarlos, y para tomar decisiones de negocio respecto de qué programas podrían gustarle a nuestros clientes.

Utilizamos información personal brindada voluntariamente para responder a sus preguntas y brindarle los servicios que usted ha solicitado, entre otros usos como se describe abajo. No vendemos ni alquilamos su información a terceros que sean proveedores de datos o empresas de marketing. Como es de esperarse, solo divulgaremos información personal cuando sea solicitado por la ley.

¿Cuándo la compartimos?

Compartimos información personal cuando es necesario para cumplir con nuestras obligaciones legales y cuando tenemos que complir con los contratos que tenemos con nuestros vendedores y negocios asociados. No le vendemos ni alquilamos ninguna información personal a terceros o intermediarios de datos, ni a empresas de marketing.  

Sus Elecciones y Derechos de Privacidad

Usted no tiene que brindar información personal para disfrutar de la mayoría de nuestras funciones en línea. Además, puede salir de determinadas actividades como de los newsletters y anuncios. Es posible que tenga ciertos derechos adicionales según la jurisdicción en la que resida, o en la que se hayan recopilado sus datos personales, de conformidad con las leyes de protección de datos aplicables.

Contacto

Las preguntas sobre esta página de aspectos destacados o nuestra declaración de privacidad en línea se pueden enviar a Etison, LLC, ATTN: Legal & Compliance Department, 3443 W. Bavaria Street, Eagle, Idaho 83616 o compliance@clickfunnels.com

La versión en inglés de esta declaración de privacidad es la versión de control independientemente de cualquier traducción que pueda intentar hacer.

NAVEGAR A TRAVÉS DE ESTA DECLARACIÓN

Puede usar los enlaces de abajo para navegar áreas de esta declaración que apliquen específicamente a usted, o que puedan ser de su interés:

Etison, LLC (“Etison,” “nosotros,” “nuestros”) gracias por visitar nuestros recursos virtuales que publicamos. Utilizamos las palabras “su” y “sus” para referirnos a ustedes, los lectores, y otros visitantes a nuestros recursos virtuales que son, en todos los casos, mayores de 13 años. Nuestra declaración de privacidad (“esta declaración”, “esta declaración de privacidad”, y “nuestra declaración”) le informa acerca de quién y los tipos de información personal que recopilamos, de cómo la usamos, con quién la compartimos y por qué, y qué hacemos para intentar protegerla.  

Los recursos virtuales son las funciones de los sitios web que poseemos que le permitirán interactuar con nuestros sitios web, así como aplicaciones que hemos creado y distribuido para permitir que nuestros clientes y seguidores vean nuestros recursos virtuales o interactúen de otra manera con el contenido que ofrecemos.

DE QUIÉN RECOPILAMOS INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Podemos recopilar información personal de los siguientes grupos de personas interesadas: visitantes y usuarios de nuestros recursos en línea y móviles; nuestros clientes; miembros actuales de nuestra fuerza laboral y aquellos que solicitan trabajos publicados; y proveedores externos y socios comerciales.

La información personal suele hacer referencia a información que puede ser utilizada para identificarlo a usted o que puede ser fácilmente unida a usted (por ejemplo su nombre, su dirección, su número telefónico, su dirección de correo electrónico, su número de seguridad social y su fecha de nacimiento). Las leyes de privacidad en algunas jurisdicciones incluyen elementos únicos en lo que consideran ser la información personal de sus consumidores o de los interesados que ellos protegen. Si esas leyes aplican a nosotros, como en el caso de La Ley de la Privacidad del Consumidor de California (“CCPA”) o El Reglamento General de Protección de Información de la UE (“GDPR”), nuestro uso de la frase “información personal” incluye los elementos únicos requeridos por dichas leyes.

Estas categorías de información que recopilamos de cada uno de estos grupos, y las formas en las que la usamos, difiere. Como podrás haber notado, es posible que la misma persona pueda entrar en más de un grupo. La mayoría de esta declaración aborda nuestro procesamiento y el intercambio de información personal recopilada de los visitantes y usuarios , y de nuestros clientes de nuestros recursos virtuales.

Sin embargo, recopilamos y retenemos los tipos de información personal profesional o relacionada con el empleado que uno esperaría que el empleador tenga acerca de su fuerza laboral actual y antigua, y de sus nuevos solicitantes de trabajo. Brindamos los avisos de recopilación legalmente solicitados, y describimos nuestro uso y difusión de la información personal de nuestra fuerza laboral y de nuestros solicitantes en mayor detalle en manuales y documentos confidenciales internos de recursos humanos accesibles a los miembros de nuestra fuerza laboral, o por publicación en los portales y aplicaciones patentados de la fuerza laboral/solicitantes que operamos. En algunos casos, los portales y las aplicaciones pueden ser manejadas por terceros que nos transfieren la información personal a nosotros. En esas situaciones, la responsabilidad legal de brindarnos el aviso es de los terceros, no nuestra.

Además como toda empresa corporativa, compramos bienes y servicios, arrendamiento de equipos y espacio para oficinas asistimos a eventos industriales. Al hacerlo, interactuamos con muchos vendedores y socios de negocios existentes y posibles a futuro, de los que necesariamente recopilamos determinada información personal conectada con nuestras relaciones de negocio contractuales. Utilizamos y compartimos información personal recopilada de nuestros vendedores y colegas para gestionar, administrar y cumplir nuestros contratos con ellos, o compartir información sobre nuestros productos. describimos el uso que hacemos de la información personal de nuestros vendedores o colegas con más detalle en los contratos confidenciales con aquellas partes, o en los portales de gestión de proveedores en los que trabajamos.

QUÉ RECOPILAMOS

Hay dos tipos de información que obtenemos de su uso en línea, y que luego almacenamos y usamos: (i) información no personal que se guarda de manera automática de cada visitante, como por ejemplo el sistema operativo que utiliza su dispositivo; y (ii) la información personal que usted nos brinda de forma voluntaria, o que se recopila automáticamente.

Al usar nuestros recursos virtuales o comprar nuestros productos o servicios, usted estará implicando que está de acuerdo con esta sección de nuestra declaración de privacidad y que podemos utilizar y divulgar su información de la forma en que lo hemos descrito.  

Información Presentada Voluntariamente. 

Si participa en determinadas actividades a través de nuestros recursos online y móviles (recursos virtuales), es posible que se le solicite que nos brinde información suya. Los tipos de información personal que recopilamos en aquellas situaciones son los identificadores (como su nombre, su dirección de correo electrónico, su dirección, y su teléfono), información profesional (como a qué negocio pertenece), e información contable financiera (como la información de su tarjeta de crédito). No le vendemos, alquilamos o intercambiamos información personal brindada voluntariamente a terceros.

Si no quiere que recopilemos este tipo de información personal, por favor no nos la brinde.  Esto quiere decir que no debería participar en las actividades virtuales que proponemos, y sería más conveniente que se comunique con nosotros por teléfono o por correo. La participación es su decisión, únicamente. No participar puede limitar su habilidad de aprovechar completamente los recursos virtuales, pero no afectará su habilidad de acceder a determinada información disponible para el público generalizado respecto a los recursos virtuales.  

Algunos ejemplos de cómo podría brindarnos voluntariamente su información personal y cómo podríamos usarla nosotros:

Correos Electrónicos y Formularios En Línea – Cuando nos envía un correo electrónico o completa un formulario en línea, ya sea para contactarnos, su correo electrónico junto con otra información personal (ej. su dirección personal o su número telefónico) que pueda estar en el contenido de su mensaje o adjunto a este, será retenida por nosotros y usada para responderle directamente y para procesar su solicitud. Dependiendo de la información personal brindada, la comunicación  de nuestra parte puede ser a través correos electrónicos, llamadas telefónicas, y/o mensajes de texto. Es probable que también le enviemos información acerca de cualquiera de nuestros productos o servicios que creamos que pueda llegar a interesarle.

Registrarse para una Cuenta – Cuando se registra para una cuenta o registra a su hijo para una subcuenta, usted nos estará brindando información personal como su nombre y su dirección de correo electrónico  (o el nombre y correo electrónico de su hijo), la cual será retenida por nosotros. Utilizamos esa información para crear y gestionar su cuenta y en algunos casos para establecer una contraseña y un perfil para comunicarnos con usted y con cualquier subcuenta que haya creado a través del correo electrónico.

Registrarse a Eventos – Cuando se registra para eventos, conferencias o programas que nosotros mismos podemos llegar a organizar (en lugar de subcontratar a un tercero que sea un gestor de eventos con sus propias políticas de privacidad), usted estará presentando los tipos de identificadores que hemos descrito anteriormente. Si el evento solicita el pago de una tarifa, es posible que solicitemos los datos de su tarjeta de crédito u otra información financiera. Usamos esta información para registrarlo al evento y para enviarle notificaciones respecto del mismo evento.

Suscribirse a Nuestro Servicio – Utilizamos cualquier información que haya sido brindada por nuestros clientes para realizar nuestras obligaciones contractuales y brindarle los productos y servicios que hayan pagado, para gestionar sus cuentas y comunicarnos con ellos.

Redes Sociales y Funciones Comunitarias – Algunos de nuestros recursos virtuales pueden ofrecer funciones comunitarias similares a las de las redes sociales, permitiéndoles a los usuarios publicar mensajes y comentarios, y/o subir una imagen u otros archivos. Si usted elige hacer uso de estas funciones, la información que suba, incluyendo su nombre en pantalla y cualquier otra información personal, estará en el dominio público y no quedará cubierto/protegido por esta declaración.

Información Recopilada Automáticamente.

Cuando visitas nuestros recursos virtuales, se recopila información básica de forma pasiva a través de su navegador, por medio del uso de tecnologías de seguimiento, como una  “cookie”, la cual es un pequeño archivo de texto que se descarga en su computadora o dispositivo móvil cuando accede a los recursos virtuales. Nos permite reconocer su computadora o dispositivo móvil y almacenar alguna información acerca de sus preferencias o acciones pasadas. Puede encontrar información adicional en nuestra [Política de Cookies](https://signup.clickfunnels.com/cookie-policy). Puede obtener más información sobre las cookies y las tecnologías de seguimiento en general [aquí](https://www.ftc.gov/site-information/privacy-policy/internet-cookies).

Les permitimos a los vendedores vendedores utilizar cookies o tecnologías similares para recopilar información sobre sus actividades de navegación por el tiempo que haya estado usando el sitio. Por ejemplo, usamos Google Analytics, un servicio de análisis web brindado por Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics utiliza cookies para ayudarnos a analizar cómo usted utiliza los recursos virtuales y mejora su experiencia cuando visita los recursos virtuales. Para más información sobre cómo utiliza Google esta información, ingrese a [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Puede conocer más sobre cómo excluirse de Google Analytics ingresando a [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

La información de la actividad de Internet recopilada a través de cookies y otros medios similares incluye cosas como: el nombre del dominio y la dirección IP desde la cual haya ingresado a nuestros recursos virtuales; el tipo de navegador y sistema operativo que haya utilizado; la fecha, hora y duración de su visita; qué página específica ha visitado,los gráficos que haya mirado y cualquier documento descargado; los enlaces específicos a otros sitios a los que hayas accedido desde nuestros recursos virtuales; y los enlaces específicos a los que hayas accedido a nuestros recursos virtuales desde otro sitio.

Además, si usted accede a nuestros recursos virtuales desde un celular u otro dispositivo móvil, el prestador de servicios móvil puede transmitirnos únicamente información identificable del dispositivo móvil, lo cual nos permitirá recopilar los números telefónicos y asociarlos con la información de identificación del dispositivo móvil. Algunos proveedores de celulares también operan sistemas que señalan la ubicación física de los dispositivos y también podemos recibir esta información si los servicios de ubicación están habilitados en su dispositivo. Si usted no quiere que nosotros utilicemos su información de geolocalización, inhabilite los servicios de ubicación en la configuración de su dispositivo.

Independientemente, utilizamos tanto información recopilada automáticamente como información del dispositivo móvil para compilar informes genéricos acerca de páginas populares sobre nuestros recursos virtuales, y para ver cómo nuestros clientes y seguidores acceden a estos recursos virtuales. Luego utilizamos esa información para administrar los recursos virtuales y mejorarlos, hacer que sus actividades sean más cómodas y eficientes, y para mejorar el funcionamiento de nuestros recursos virtuales, por ejemplo recordando determinada información suya para ahorrarle tiempo.

Utilizamos y retenemos su información personal de acuerdo con las leyes siempre que sea necesario para llevar a cabo los propósitos descritos anteriormente de acuerdo con nuestros procedimientos de retención internos.  

El Usuario Debe Tener Cuidado de: Los Sitios, Apps, Enlaces y Redes Sociales Externos.

Mantenemos una presencia en más de una plataforma de redes sociales, como Twitter, Facebook, YouTube y LinkedIn. Además, podemos permitir que las funciones de nuestros recursos virtuales se conecten con, o sean visibles desde, esa presencia externa en las redes sociales. De forma similar, nuestros recursos virtuales pueden contener enlaces a otros sitios webs o apps que estén controlados por terceros.

No somos responsables ni del contenido, ni de las políticas de privacidad de las plataformas de redes sociales, ni de cualquier sitio web o aplicación de terceros a los que estemos unidos. Aquellas apps, sitios y plataformas no están controlados por nosotros y, por lo tanto, tienen sus propias políticas de privacidad y términos de uso. Si tiene preguntas acerca de cómo esas apps, sitios y plataformas recopilan y utilizan información personal, debe leer sus políticas de privacidad detalladamente y contactarlos utilizando la información que brinden.

CUÁNDO/CON QUIÉN COMPARTIMOS INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Utilizamos información no personal para administrar nuestros recursos virtuales, mejorarlos, y para tomar decisiones de negocio respecto de qué programas podrían gustarles a nuestros clientes.  

Utilizamos información personal brindada de forma voluntaria para nuestros intereses legítimos, incluyendo la respuesta a sus preguntas y para poder brindarle los servicios que haya solicitado, entre otros usos que se describirán más adelante. No vendemos o alquilamos su información personal a terceros que sean vendedores de información o empresas de marketing. Como usted podría esperar, solo revelamos su información cuando la ley lo solicite. Podemos usar su información personal cuando tengamos su consentimiento para hacerlo, cuando sea necesario o permitido bajo leyes aplicables.

Afiliados.

Además de los terceros establecidos anteriormente, podemos compartir su información, incluyendo su información personal, dentro de nuestra familia de empresas. Esas empresas usarán esa información de la misma manera en que nosotros lo hacemos, lo cual incluye enviarle información sobre sus productos, servicios o iniciativas que puedan ser de interés para usted.  

Obligación Legal a Difundir Información.

Podemos llegar a divulgar su información, incluyendo su información personal, a las autoridades gubernamentales, y a otros terceros cuando nos veamos obligados a hacerlo por las autoridades gubernamentales, o a nuestra discreción o según lo requiera o permita la ley, lo que incluye, entre otros, responder a órdenes judiciales y citaciones.

Impedir Daños.

Podemos divulgar su información, incluyendo su información personal, cuando tengamos razones para creer que alguien está causando daños o interfiriendo con nuestros derechos o propiedad, con otros usuarios de nuestros recursos virtuales, o con cualquier otro que pudiera verse afectado por tales actividades.

Traspaso de Empresa.

Si nosotros o cualquiera de nuestros afiliados, o sustancialmente todos sus activos son adquiridos por uno o más terceros como resultado de una adquisición, fusión, venta, reorganización, consolidación o liquidación, la información personal puede ser uno de los activos transferidos.

Vendedores y Socios Comerciales.

Podemos compartir su información, incluyendo su información personal, con nuestros vendedores y otros terceros con los que tengamos relaciones contractuales. Además podemos compartir su información, incluyendo su información personal, con vendedores que brinden servicios de software que usted haya elegido para asistirlo con sus embudos de ventas. Hacemos lo mejor para divulgar únicamente la información que cada una de esas partes necesite.

Hemos adoptado normas para aquellos vendedores y socios comerciales que hayan recibido información personal de nuestra parte. Intentamos unir a dichos vendedores y socios comerciales a aquellas normas a través de contratos escritos. Intentamos restringir contractualmente lo que nuestros vendedores y socios comerciales puedan hacer con la información personal que les brindamos ya que solo se utiliza para llevar a cabo el objetivo de negocio para el cual se haya brindado;  no se divulga a nadie más sin nuestro consentimiento o bajo nuestras instrucciones; sigue siendo, entre nosotros y el proveedor o socio comercial correspondiente, nuestra propiedad; y no se transfiere fuera de los Estados Unidos sin nuestro consentimiento.

Sin embargo, por favor tenga en cuenta que no podemos garantizar que todos nuestros vendedores y socios comerciales estén de acuerdo con estos requisitos contractuales; ni tampoco podemos asegurar que, incluso al acceder, cumplan siempre.

SUS DERECHOS Y OPCIONES

Puede optar por no proporcionar información personal, pero al hacerlo, es posible que algunas de las funciones de nuestros recursos en línea y móviles no estén disponibles para usted. Además, puede optar por no participar en ciertas actividades, como boletines y anuncios. Los interesados en ciertos lugares, o cuyos datos personales se obtuvieron mientras se encontraban en ciertos lugares, pueden tener derechos adicionales de conformidad con las leyes de protección de datos aplicables.

Jurisdicción GDPR significa que los países que componen el Área Económica Europea, El Reino Unido (que pronto dejará la Unión Europea), Suiza y Japón, habiendo recibido una “decisión de adecuación” por parte de la Comisión Europea, adhiere a los términos materiales de la GDPR.

Si estamos utilizando información personal que usted nos haya brindado para permitirnos enviarle materiales, como newsletters y alertas de productos a través de mensajes de texto email, y decide que no quiere seguir recibiendo dicho material, puedes salirte siguiendo las instrucciones para hacerlo en el email u otras comunicaciones (ej. respondiendo al mensaje de texto con “PARAR”), o contactandonos utilizando la información de contacto de abajo.  Cuando recibamos su solicitud, tomaremos los pasos razonables para eliminar su nombre de nuestra lista de distribución. Debe entender que puede llevarnos algún tiempo eliminar su nombre de nuestras listas de contacto luego de su petición y debido a dicha latencia puede seguir recibiendo materiales durante algún periodo de tiempo luego de haberse retirado. Además de retirarse, tiene la habilidad de acceder, modificar, y eliminar su información personal contactandonos utilizando la información personal de abajo.

Algunos navegadores tienen una función de “no rastreo” que permite especificarle a los sitios web que no quieres que se rastreen tus actividades en línea. En este momento no respondemos específicamente a las señales de “no rastrear” del navegador.

PRIVACIDAD DE LOS NIÑOS 

Las leyes federales imponen restricciones especiales y obligaciones sobre los operadores de sitios web que dirigen sus operaciones hacia, y recopilan y utilizan información de niños menores a 13 años. Nos tomamos esos requisitos muy seriamente, y teniendo en cuenta eso no esperamos que nuestros recursos virtuales sean usados por niños menores de 13 años sin antes haber obtenido el consenso verificable de los padres o el tutor legal del niño. Además, no recopilamos a sabiendas información personal de menores de 13 años, solo un padre o tutor legal puede proporcionar dicha información después de adherirse a nuestro proceso de verificación para enviar dicha información a través de los recursos virtuales.  Si notamos que cualquier persona menor de 18 años ha ingresado información personal a nuestros recursos virtuales sin la aprobación de sus padres o tutores legales, y que no es una parte integral para acceder o utilizar nuestros Servicios, eliminaremos la información y no la utilizaremos para nada. Si usted cree que un menor de 18 años ha ingresado información personal a nuestros recursos virtuales, por favor contáctenos a compliance@clickfunnels.com. Alentamos a los padres y tutores legales a hablar con sus hijos acerca de los riesgos potenciales de brindar su información personal en internet.

CÓMO PROTEGEMOS LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL RECOPILADA

Tomaremos todas las precauciones de seguridad para proteger la información personal que nos haya brindado al utilizar nuestros recursos virtuales. Hemos adoptado un programa que incluye medidas técnicas, organizacionales, administrativas y de seguridad, diseñado para proteger, de forma consistente con las normas y leyes industriales aceptadas, en contra de las amenazas anticipadas o que están realmente sucediendo contra la seguridad de la información personal  (el “Programa de Seguridad”). Sin embargo, no podemos garantizar que su información, ya sea durante la transmisión de la misma o cuando ya esté almacenada en nuestros sistemas, esté completamente libre de accesos no autorizados, o que no vaya a ocurrir la pérdida, el uso indebido, la destrucción o la alteración de la misma. Excepto por nuestro deber de mantener el Programa de Seguridad según la ley aplicable, renunciamos a cualquier otra responsabilidad por cualquier robo o pérdida, acceso no autorizado o daño o interceptación de cualquier dato o comunicación, incluida la información personal. Tenemos todo la razón de creer que nuestro Sistema de Seguridad es razonable y apropiado para nuestro negocio y para la naturaleza de los riesgos previsibles que atentan contra la información personal que recopilamos. Además revisamos y actualizamos periódicamente nuestro Programa de Seguridad, como lo solicita la ley aplicable.

No obstante, como parte de nuestro Programa de Seguridad, tenemos una respuesta a los incidentes específicos y gestión de procedimientos que se activa en cualquier momento que sepamos que tu información personal pueda haber estado comprometida. Además, requerimos, como parte de nuestros procedimientos de supervisión de vendedores y socios comerciales, que dichas partes nos notifiquen de inmediato si tienen algún motivo para creer que ha ocurrido un incidente que afectó negativamente la información personal que les proporcionamos.

LA LEY DE LA PRIVACIDAD DEL CONSUMIDOR DE CALIFORNIA

Cuando recopilamos información personal de los residentes de California, estamos sujetos a la Ley de Privacidad del Consumidor de California, y esos residentes tienen derechos en virtud de esta. Esta sección de nuestra declaración se usa para permitirnos cumplir con nuestras obligaciones de la CCPA y explicar tus derechos CCPA.  Para los propósitos de esta sección, las palabras “usted” y “su” harán referencia a los residentes de California.

¿Qué Recopilamos de los Residentes de  California?

Recopilamos las siguientes categorías de información personal: identificadores como el nombre, dirección, dirección IP, y otros identificadores personales; información personal descrita en la subdivisión (e) de la Sección 1798.80 (Estatuto de clientes de California) como el nombre, dirección, número telefónico, número de tarjeta de crédito; información comercial como los productos o servicios comprados; actividad de internet/electrónica como el historial de navegación y el historial de búsqueda; información de geolocalización incluyendo las coordenadas geográficas/ubicación física; e información de audio, video, electrónica o similar.  hemos difundido estas categorías de información con propósito de negocio dentro de los últimos 12 meses. No vendemos, ni hemos venido dentro de los últimos 12 meses, información personal a terceros.

Derechos de los Residentes de California

Tiene los siguientes derechos bajo la CCPA, en resúmen divulgación, acceso y eliminación. Puede encontrar más información [aquí](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division=3.&part=4.&lawCode=CIV&title=1.81.5). Para nosotros es importante que usted sepa que si  ejerce estos derechos, no lo “discriminaremos” tratándolo distinto de otros residentes californianos que utilizan nuestros sitios y recursos virtuales o compran nuestros servicios pero no ejercen sus derechos.

Puedes ejercer estos derechos hasta dos veces cada 12 meses. Para hacerlo, debes contactarnos a [compliance@clickfunnels.com](mailto:compliance@clickfunnels.com) o 1-888-411-0243. Es posible que le solicitemos que llene un formulario de solicitud. La CCPA únicamente nos permite actuar sobre su solicitud si podemos verificar su identidad o su autoridad para haber realizado la petición, así que también será necesario que siga nuestras instrucciones para verificar su identidad.

Si realizas una solicitud verificable teniendo en cuenta lo anterior, confirmaremos nuestro recibo y responderemos en los tiempos prescritos por la CCPA.

EL REGLAMENTO GENERAL DE PROTECCIÓN DE INFORMACIÓN DE LA UE

Recopilamos u obtenemos información personal de los interesados ubicada en la Jurisdicción GDPR. Cumplimos con nuestras obligaciones GDPR con respecto a nuestra fuerza laboral/solicitantes de empleo, nuestros clientes (y sus propios clientes finales), y nuestros vendedores y socios laborales a través de una serie de avisos separados, contratos u otros términos que se les brinda en el momento, de la forma que corresponde, como lo requiere la GPDR y la ley local dentro de cada Jurisdicción GDPR.

Describimos, en la sección que sigue en esta declaración, cómo cumplimos con la GDPR por la información personal recopilada de de los visitantes y usuarios de nuestros recursos virtuales, mientras que estaban en una Jurisdicción GPDR. Así, por los fines de esta sección, las palabras “usted” y “su” hace referencia únicamente a los visitantes y usuarios basados en la Jurisdicción GDPR.

¿Qué recopilamos de usted en las Jurisdicciones GDPR y cómo lo utilizamos?

De usted recopilamos las categorías de información personal que ya han sido descritas.  La base legal en la cual nos apoyamos para dicha recopilación, para su uso y divulgación posterior, es a lo que la GDPR se refiere como interés legítimo. Como se ya mencionado en otra sección de este apartado, no vendemos ninguna parte de su información personal a terceros ni la utilizamos para tomar decisiones de forma automática.

Transferencia de Datos entre Estados y Procesador de Terceros

Si transferimos información personal de las Jurisdicciones de la GDPR a una ubicación que no esté considerada de tener protecciones de privacidad adecuadas por la Comisión Europea, haremos lo que la GDPR permita.  

Derechos de los Interesados en las Jurisdicciones de la GDPR

Mientras intentamos permitirles a todos nuestros visitantes y usuarios de nuestros recursos virtuales a ejercitar cierto grado de control sobre su información personal, siguiendo a la GDPR tenemos una obligación legal de hacerlo por usted. Más específicamente, con respecto a la información personal recopilada de usted mientras estaba en una Jurisdicción GDPR, tiene estos derechos: transparencia, acceso, corrección y eliminación, portabilidad, quién, qué y dónde, y restricción/objeción (para más información, haga clic [aquí](https://gdpr-info.eu/chapter-3/)).

Si quiere ejercer cualquiera de estos derechos, por favor contacte a [compliance@clickfunnels.com](mailto:compliance@clickfunnels.com). Su habilidad de ejercer estos derechos está sujeta a determinadas condiciones y exenciones de las que puede leer en los artículos 12 a 23 de la GDPR. Entre estas condiciones se encuentra nuestro derecho a declinar parte o toda la petición si no podemos satisfacer nuestras dudas y preocupaciones razonables acerca de su identidad de una manera que nos ayude a minimizar el riesgo de que una persona no autorizada pueda utilizar un derecho de la GDPR para acceder a su información personal. Responderemos a todas las solicitudes sin retraso, teniendo en cuenta los plazos, si es que los hay, prescritos por la GDPR. Si usted no está satisfecho con cómo utilizamos su información personal o la forma en que respondemos a sus peticiones, tiene el derecho a quejarse con su regulador de protección de datos. La información de contacto de los reguladores de protección de información de la UE puede encontrarse [aquí](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080).  

De conformidad con el artículo 27 del GDPR, puede ponerse en contacto con nuestro representante de la UE utilizando la siguiente información de contacto:

IITR Datenschutz GmbH

Marienplatz 2, 80331 München, Germany

email@iitr.de

089-1891736

DERECHOS DE LOS INTERESADOS EN OTRA JURISDICCIÓN

En otras jurisdicciones, con regulaciones similares en cuanto a la privacidad de los datos, es probable que podamos recopilar las categorías de información personal suya que ya han sido descritas. Recopilamos y gestionamos (incluyendo la divulgación) dicha información de conformidad con las leyes locales aplicables. Como se ha señalado, no vendemos ningún tipo de información personal a terceros, ni la utilizamos para la toma de decisiones automáticas.

CAMBIOS A ESTA DECLARACIÓN DE PRIVACIDAD

La versión en inglés de esta declaración de privacidad es la versión principal, sin importar cualquier otra traducción que usted pueda intentar.

Nos reservamos el derecho a cambiar o actualizar esta declaración en algún momento. Por favor revise nuestros recursos virtuales de forma periódica para enterarse de dichos cambios, ya que toda la información recopilada está sujeta a la declaración en vigencia en ese momento.  

CONTACTO

Si tiene preguntas acerca de nuestra declaración o prácticas de privacidad, por favor contáctenos a:

Etison, LLC

Attn: Legal & Compliance Department

3443 W. Bavaria Street

Eagle, Idaho 83616

compliance@clickfunnels.com

Copyright 2023 - Etison LLC dba ClickFunnels - All Rights Reserved

Working...
----------
